fairtradetraffic.com 2014-11-25

# Fair Trade Traffic Manual Surf Exchange

* * *

**This Privacy Policy applies to all accounts registered via FairTradeTraffic.com**  
Use of the FairTradeTraffic.com website and related services constitutes explicit acknowledgement of these policies.

**Information Collection and Use of Information**  
In order to use the member services onsite, all users must first complete the registration form fully and accurately, including desired username, valid email address, real name, and country of residence. During registration all users are required to provide a valid email address that must be verified. Such email is used to contact the user about website news, events, and promotions. We will not sell, share, or rent this address or any other personal information to others.

**Security**  
Our Company takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, it is stored immediately with our hosting partners. Only our administrative team can access users' personal information and membership rosters. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes  
such change can be updated and saved within the member profile page at anytime.

**Right to Cancel**  
Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases at anytime. Any user can delete his/her own account by simply following the steps provided within the member profile. Alternately, any member may opt-out of sponsored newsletters via profile options. However, opt-out from administrative site news can only be achieved via full account deletion.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We send all users website and service announcement updates periodically via email. We may also communicate with users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts (or advertising content) via email.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Users will receive notification of updates to this policy via administrative email, and always have the option to review again this publicly posted information.

**Questions?**  

Are you following my blog?  
Free tips, blogging ideas, traffic and more!

* * *
